Today's truth of looting from this is
good, on one hand Lipika graduated from her career,
now see, there is more
consolidation recording, then you would be
advised to try it on the room for 50 years
and it is 1627, okay,
target up to 100 in ICICI Lombard and today you also heard that news
in CNBC Awaaz, first of all we
told you early in the morning that the decision to increase the
FD limit for insurance companies by 74 percent has
now been
notified and implemented and this is the
reason that today you are seeing a good trend in insurance companies,
Edwardo stock which is
liked by everyone, target of 16 is 1492, you will
place this top, let's see the next big one, before that
quickly see today's Africa has risen, do it
and today's method is train, Gujarat Sidhi
Cement, skip cement, let's talk continuously, this is the
stock where a press break is
seen today and in this, we have
looked at this topic today, it is exactly
on your screen or technically what you  You'll be able to see this.
Look, these Didi
charts are in front of you, and here you can see that
it was stuck in a consolidation zone
from February until now. You see this breakout from the top February-March,
April, and almost four months of
consolidation. It's
also worth noting today's cement from Gujarat.
You're seeing a tremendous rally in all cement stocks right now,
and any
question mark (Q-line) that appears
is a sign that you
may see more opportunities in the stock.
Secondly, during the recent problems in Gujarat, the
losses caused by the cyclone, the
demand for cement is likely to increase further
because the government is fully
committed to helping the people.
It's one thing, and
another thing is that during this time, when work is shut down,
you see that infrastructure construction is
steadily decreasing, and therefore, the
demand for cement seems to be consistently improving. There does
n't seem to be any significant problem. The company has offered it at a lower rate.
They closed their plant for two days,
but this
They haven't suffered any losses due to the cyclone.
I'm bringing you the weekly
chart because you'll
see the picture getting better. You can see
that there was a consolidation pattern.
You've gotten a little bit of a breakout from that this week. The
bulk of this breakout actually came today. If you look
at the bigger picture,
you can get an idea of ​​how far the run could open.
Didi, but you're seeing a very
clear-cut breakout forming today.
Ashmit's Chart Manager
for cement stocks is constantly in the news.
This page is printed out in front of you. The
correction team
looked at the consolidation, and it shows a bell coming out of the consolidation.
Generally, the volume is low. But the recent
volume activity we've
seen here is a bit encouraging.
From here, there will be a collection of twenty-six,
which is the recent swimming. As for the
levels, you
can also see a committee array card in it. Then, it can
also reflect the staff.